Finding Aid for the Ana Bégué de Packman papers, 1870-1960 LSC.1491
UCLA Library Special Collections
- California missions, ca. 1880-1965; 2.5 boxes
  - Mission San Juan Capistrano, ca. 1933-1951 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    Photographs, clippings, a typewritten page with the Spanish-language epitaph for Antonio Yorba, and additional typescripts. Eleven handwritten pages of notes by Packman pertaining to ranchos in Orange County and cattle holdings by members of the Yorba, Sepulveda, Ruiz, O'Campo, and Avila families.
  - Mission San Luís Obispo, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Mission San Luís Rey de Francia (1 of 2), ca. 1938-1963 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    Postcards, photographs and printed ephemera.
  - Mission San Luís Rey de Francia (2 of 2), ca. 1880-1956 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    Photographs. Images include: Packman, Marco Newpark, and attorney Joseph Scott on a Historical Society visit to the Mission; various priests and persons, including an Indian woman named Bacella (ca. 1899); and the buildings and grounds.
  - Mission San Miguel Arcángel, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 12)
    Photographs and clippings. Images include: Father Ignatius in the garden at Mission San Miguel; olive crusher in the mission courtyard; the mission before and after restoration.
  - Mission San Rafael Arcángel, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 13)
    Postcard.
  - Mission Santa Bárbara--Miscellaneous, ca. 1898-1957 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    Notes, printed ephemera and research materials.
  - Mission Santa Bárbara--Photographs, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 2)
    Exterior views of the mission and photographs of priests.
  - Mission Santa Clara de Asís, ca. 1937 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    Photographs, postcards and clippings.
  - Mission Santa Inés (Santa Cruz), ca. 1934-1935 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    Photographs, postcards and printed ephemera.
- Ranchos and adobes, ca. 1845-1962; 3 boxes (1.5 linear ft.)
  Photographs, clippings, notes and Packman's own manuscripts relating to the history of California ranchos and adobes. Arranged alphabetically by folder title. See box 14 for a folder of oversize newspapers clippings about Southern California ranchos and California families, mostly historical in nature.
  - Rancho Aguaje de Centinela, ca. 1933-1946 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    Photograph, notes and clippings.
  - Rancho Cañada de Santa Ana, ca. 1940 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    Packman's handwritten notes pertaining to brands of Irvine County; June 1940 issue of The Quarterly (Historical Society of Southern California publication).
  - Rancho de La Ballona--Miscellaneous, ca. 1955 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    Clippings, manuscripts and printed ephemera. Includes a detailed genealogy of the Higuera family.
  - Rancho de La Ballona--Photographs, ca. 1870-1940 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    Photographs. Images include: De Bartolo Winery (ca. 1939); Talamantes Adobe ruins in Culver City (ca. 1939); Machado hacienda (ca. 1870); the Higuera-Chapman family, including Francisco Higuera, Enrique Higuera, Secundio Higuera, Manuela Higuera, Rosario Higuera, Bernardo Higuera, Estevan Higuera, Maria Chapman, Joseph Chapman, Juan Chapman, Eva Chapman, Juanita Chapman, and Claudena Olvera; Captain and Mrs. Timms (ca. 1880); and various photographs of La Ballona and Port Ballona.
  - Rancho de La Brea, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 5)
    Photographs, clippings, manuscripts and printed ephemera.
  - Rancho de La Cienega O' Paso de la Tijera, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 6)
    Photographs of a map and the Sanchez adobe.
  - Rancho de la Isla de Santa Catalina--Miscellaneous, ca. 1890 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    Postcards, photographs and clippings. Handwritten transcription by Geneva Wheeler of the diary of Frank Le Couvrer.
  - Rancho de la Isla de Santa Catalina---Photographs, ca. 1880-1900 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    Photographs. Images include: bay and city of Avalon; Seal Rock; Sugar Loaf; Bath House; Chef from Hotel Metropole with the catch of the day, labeled as a "Catalina Island Jew Fish."
  - Rancho de la Merced, ca. 1869-1937 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    Notes and photographs of the Rafael Bayse adobe and the Juan Matias Sanchez home.
  - Rancho La Puente (Temple / Workman Ranch), ca. 1845-1923 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    Research materials pertaining to the John Temple / Alfred Workman Ranch. Photographs include: an adobe or ranch house on Valley Boulevard in El Monte; the site of the old John Rowland adobe; Walter P. Temple Memorial / Pio Pico mausoleum; Alfred Workman wine cellar and adobe; home of Walter P. Temple; home of Sheriff John Rowland; and three women in front of the John Rowland ranch.
  - Rancho de las Cienegas, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 11)
    Packman's notes and a three-page typewritten report entitled "Rancho de Las Cienegas."
  - Rancho de los Cerritos, ca. 1880-1933 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    Photographs of various subjects, including: John Temple ranch house at Rancho de los Cerritos; tourists and sunbathers at Long Beach (ca. 1887); wharf, bath house and pier at Long Beach near Ocean Boulevard and Magnolia Avenue (ca. 1890); swimming costumes; promenade at Long Beach (ca. 1905); Long Beach at Pine Avenue (ca. 1900); Devil's Gate, present-day Belmont Beach in Los Alamitos (ca. 1908); artesian well in Long Beach; Hotel Virginia; and oil derricks.
  - Rancho de los Coyotes, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 13)
    Packman's notes.
  - Rancho de los Encinos, ca. 1946 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    Notes and manuscripts.
  - Rancho de Los Feliz, ca. 1890-1910 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    Photographs and printed ephemera. Images include: Catalina Verdugo adobe at La Cañada; Los Feliz adobe; Teodoro Verdugo adobe and the Oak of Peace.
  - Rancho de Los Palos Verdes, ca. 1900-1959 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    Photographs, clippings and notes.
  - Rancho El Tejon, ca. 1900-1955 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Rancho Jurupa, ca. 1800-1950 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    Photographs and notes. Images include: Casa Loma ranch house; stage station in Palm Springs; home of Antonio or Francisco Estudillo in San Jacinto, Riverside; Good Hope mine on Ortega Road in Perris Valley, Riverside (ca. 1943); adobe on North Canyon Drive, Palm Springs; Juan Machado adobe in Lake Elsinore; Courthouse; Glenwood Cottage / Mission Inn; Luis Rubidoux Rancho (ca. 1860-1921); President Theodore Roosevelt planting a navel orange tree at the Mission Inn in Riverside; Indians at the Agua Mansa Rancheria; and Pechanga Reservation.
  - Rancho Paso de Bartolo, ca. 1890-1940 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    Postcards, clippings, Packman's notes, and photographs of Pio Pico's adobe at Rancho Paso de Bartolo.
  - Rancho Repetto, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 6)
    Clippings and an article.
  - Rancho Rincón de los Bueyes, ca. 1885, 1940 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    Photographs and notes.
  - Rancho Rodeo de las Aguas--Miscellaneous, ca. 1934-1938, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    Pamphlets, clippings and notes.
  - Rancho Rodeo de las Aguas--Photographs, ca. 1900-1930 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    Photographs include: the ranch house at Rodeo de las Aguas; house of Doña Maria Rita Valdez de Villa; view of Beverly Hills from the Beverly Hills Hotel; aerial photographs of the Mercury Aviation Company airfield, with a view of oil wells and Hammel bean fields; Beverly Hills mayor Will Rogers; early development; trolley station; Beverly Hills Raceway on Wilshire (ca. 1921); Denker and Hammel creamery on Pruess Road (later Robertson Boulevard); and Benjamin "Don Benito" Davis Wilson's cattle on Rancho Rodeo de las Aguas.
  - Rancho San Antonio, ca. 1890-1910 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    Photographs include: Lugo Adobe ruins on E. Washington; Lugo House bedroom; Ballesteros sisters; Henry T. Gage's ranch house; Lugo adobe (ca. 1890) and family members including Vicenta Pérez, Victoria Avila Lugo, Felipe Lugo, Toney Lugo, Vicente Lugo, Pedro Lugo, Andres Lugo, and Geo. Merrill. Packman's notes and a plat map reproduction.
  - Rancho San Francisco (1 of 2), ca. 1926-1934 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    Ephemera and manuscripts.
  - Rancho San Francisco (2 of 2), ca. 1850-1910 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    Notes and photographs. Images include: Rancho Camulos (ca. 1906); members of the del Valle family (the inspiration for the Helen Hunt Jackson novel Ramona); Señora Ysabell Varela del Valle; Josefa del Valle de Forster; street scenes at Newhall, California; and the Santa Clarita Valley.
  - Rancho San José (1 of 2), ca. 1937-1960 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    Notes, manuscripts and research materials.
  - Rancho San José (2 of 2), ca. 1860-1940 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    Notes and photographs. Images include: Palomares adobe (ca. 1934); gravesites of Francisca Lopez Arvizu and Don Ygnacio Palomares; downtown Pomona; La Casa de Saturnino Carrion near San Dimas; William Rubottom Hotel and Stage Station (ca. 1867) on Rancho San José; Ygnacio Palomares ranch house; Ontario and San Antonio Heights Railroad Company railcar; Los Nogales ranch house in Spadra, owned by Don Ramon Vejar; Palomares Hotel; and the adobe at Bear Canyon, south of Walnut.
  - Rancho San Pasqual, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Rancho San Pedro--Miscellaneous, ca. 1942-1960 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Rancho San Pedro--Photographs (1 of 3), ca. 1900-1931 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    Photographs include: the Dominguez Adobe ranch house at Rancho San Pedro; whale fishermen in San Pedro; original Manuel Dominguez adobe ruins; Louis Paulhan making an altitude flight at Dominguez Airpark (ca. 1910); Howard Gill flying a Wright plane at Dominguez Airpark (ca. January 1912); Union Oil Co. wells at Signal Hill, Long Beach (ca. 1924); oil fire at Point Fermin, California (ca. 1923); S. S. Wortley oil wells at Signal Hill (ca. 1931).
  - Rancho San Pedro--Photographs (2 of 3), ca. 1850-1910 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    Photographs include the Camp Drum barracks in Wilmington and views of the wharf.
  - Rancho San Pedro--Photographs (3 of 3), ca. 1886-1910 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    Photographs of San Pedro Harbor, Dead Man's Island, and nearby businesses and streets.
  - Rancho San Rafael--Miscellaneous, ca. 1926-1932 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Rancho San Rafael--Photographs, ca. 1850-1930 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    Images include: Verdugo Adobe; Eagle Rock trolley car; la Piedra Gorda (the Fat Rock); homes of Tomas Sanchez and E. H. Gould at La Crescenta (ca. 1888); and the Sanchez Adobe at Rancho San Rafael.
  - Rancho San Vicente y Santa Monica--Miscellaneous, ca. 1952-1962 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Rancho San Vicente y Santa Monica--Photographs, ca. 1850-1910 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    Images include: T. A. Sanchez and John Wilson; Castle Rock; adobe of Dolores Sepulveda at Rancho San Vicente; Santa Monica beach and Arch Rock; and local landmarks and businesses.
  - Rancho Santa Anita--Miscellaneous, ca. 1947-1960 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    Notes and printed ephemera. See box 14 for oversize newspapers clippings about Rancho Santa Anita and the race track.
  - Rancho Santa Anita--Photographs, ca. 1890 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    Images include Baldwin Park and Rancho Santa Anita; Queen Anne Cottage; Baldwin Ranch (ca. 1890); adobe home of Hugo Reid; and other local scenes.
  - Rancho Santa Gertrudes--Miscellaneous, ca. 1951 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Rancho Santa Gertrudes--Photographs, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 12)
    Images include the Ramirez family and Lemuel Carpenter's Los Nietos Ranch (bought by José Ramirez in 1856).
  - Rancho Santa Rosa, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 13)
    Photographs. Images include: Pechanga Indian church, cemetery, and the Coahuilla Indian cemetery; the Juan Moreno adobe; and the areas of Temecula and Lake Elsinore.
  - Rancho Sausal Redondo, ca. 1900 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    Photographs and copies of images of Redondo Beach and the pier.
  - Rancho Tajauta, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 15)
    Article.
  - Rancho Topanga Malibu Sequiet, ca. 1910 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    Printed materials and photographs of Rancho Topanga Malibu canyon, Fernwood Park, and Topanga Canyon.
- Miscellaneous, ca. 1850-1976; 3 boxes (1.5 linear ft.)
  Miscellaneous research files on a variety of topics, including two folders of material related to Packman's publications Leather Dollars and Early California Hospitality. Files contain photographs, clippings, notes and manuscripts.
  - Goat Island (Yerba Buena), San Francisco, Calif. (Box 10, Folder 1)
    Photograph of the island from across the harbor.
  - San Francisco, Calif., ca. 1846 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    Photograph of a illustration of San Francisco's Montgomery Street, drawn from the harbor perspective.
  - French pioneers in California, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 3)
    Photographs of Jean Luis Vignes, George Mensager, Jean-Louis Sainsevain, Theodor Maximilian Ferdinand Franz Lecouvreur, Jose Mascrell, Jean Bernard (husband to Susana Machado), Charles Ducommon, and Joseph Mesmer.
  - Missions, ca. 1917-1957 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    Brochures and printed ephemera related to visiting the California missions.
  - California sporting history, ca. 1932 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    Photographs of artworks, and a typewritten manuscript entitled "Corrida de Toros."
  - California women, ca. 1850-1910 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    Photographs. Images include: Mary Emily Foy; Eliza Madigan; the Volney E. Howard family including Mrs. Catharine Elizabeth Howard' Mrs. Joshua Reed Giddings (probably Jennie Hollingsworth Giddings) of Pasadena; Mrs. Osoro W. Childs II, Fiesta Queen in 1894; Louise Ward Watkins; Anita Johnson Mellus de Trudell; Helen Hunt Jackson; Grace Mellus Thomas; and a photograph of a portrait of Mrs. Anita Johnson Mellus de Trudell (wife of Henry Mellus).
  - Californios, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 7)
    Photographs and images of Don José Maria Covarrubias and Don Miguel de los Rios, General Victor Castro, Santiago E. Argüello, and George Edward Hall.
  - Cattle Brands of Early California manuscript (1 of 2), ca. 1967 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    Handwritten and typewritten notes for a manuscript tracing cattle brands and genealogies among southern California's early Spanish-Mexican families, specifically the Nieto, Olvera, Sepulveda, and Yorba families. The main source of information appears to be Los Angeles County brand books, the oldest dating back to 1835.
  - Cattle Brands of Early California manuscript (2 of 2), ca. 1967 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    Additional notes and manuscript material. Includes a photograph of a chart entitled "The First Brands Registered in Each County of California" prepared by Bert Sooy.
  - Alvarado family, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 10)
    Photographs of members of the Alvarado family, including Juan Bautista Valentín Alvarado y Vallejo, Adolfo Rivera outside the Casa de Cahuenga, José Antonio Serrano, Anna Grazide Alvarado and Margarite Grazide Pillario, José Francisco Alvarado, Rendon y Alvarado de Carrillo, Narcissa Alvarado de los Rios, and others.
  - Native Americans, ca. 1885-1933 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    Assorted research materials. Photographs include images of Southern California Indians, such as Jose Pedro Losero, a Saboba Indian (ca. 1899); Capitan Pedro Pablo and others in front of his house (ca. 1885); Rojerio, the chorister of San Fernando; and others.
  - California Herald, 1967 June-July (Box 10, Folder 12)
    Official publication of The Native Daughters of the Golden West.
  - Early Californians, ca. 1924-1932 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    Photographs of descendants of early Californians, including: Adela Thompson y de la Osa; Ricardo and Francisco Viejar; Eugene Plummer; Don Manuel Sazueta (ca. 1924); Mr. W. Patter at the Repetto rancho (in present-day Monterey Park); Leo E. Triggs Revera standing at the site of the Don Luís Botillier adobe; Casildo Aguilar; Victoria Rains, wife of Governor Gage; and Judge Augustín Olvera.
  - Texas missions, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 14)
    Postcards of Mission San José and Mission de La Purisima Conception in San Antonio, Texas.
  - El Molino Viejo, ca. 1885 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    Postcards and photographs.
  - Riverside County, ca. 1890 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    Photograph of a school built in 1889 alongside Corona-Ellsinore Road in Temescal Canyon; assorted photographs of adobe ruins and structures.
  - Gage family, ca. 1850-1931 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    Photographs of the Gage home and various family members, including Lucy Gage as an infant, Robert Rains, Luisa Carrillo Curry, Lucy Gage Rand, Henry T. Gage and other unidentified people. Also includes printed ephemera, such as invitations and announcements, and notes.
  - William G. Dryden, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 1)
    Photograph of a portrait of Judge William G. Dryden, and a one-page typed biography.
  - Kern County Historical Society, 1949-1950 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    Correspondence and Kern County Historical Society newsletters, dating from January to May 1950.
  - Miscellaneous photographs (1 of 2), ca. 1880-1930 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    Photographs from a folder originally labeled "North Americans." Images include: Benjamin D. Wilson and his son, John Wilson; John C. Campbell; William R. Rowland; William Bettis; Tomas Sanchez; Rabbi Edelman; Jacob Rich; Henry D. Barrows; Thomas Delano; Felix J. Zeehandelaar; Frank Wiggins; Greek George; Thomas Scully (ca. 1926); F. C. Shurtleff; President and Mrs. McKinley (ca. 1901); Alfred Robinson; Samuel D. Hunter; Don Carlos Johnson; Tiburcio Vasquez and his captors; a group shot of General Phineas Banning, Mathew Keller, and Col. John H. Hollister; William H. Workman and John King; David Alexander; Andrew Glassell; John Jones; John Lanfranco; Isaac Lankershim; Louis Phillips; Billy Warren; James Miller Guinn; Ferdinand Nicolay and his parents; Rockwell D. Hunt; Victor Chevallier (ca. 1884); Mr. and Mrs. C. C. Thomas; Mr. and Mrs. de Mellus; Mr. and Mrs. Ozro W. Childs; William R. Rowland; Gen. Charles Foreman; and unidentified persons.
  - Miscellaneous photographs (2 of 2), ca. 1850-1950 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    Photographs and notes related to Packman's research. Images include: beach scenes; a photograph of a man playing a guitar, with a handwritten dedication to Doña Elvira Winston signed by Charles Lummis; Mr. and Mrs. Benjamin D. Wilson; Eugene Plummer, head of a dance troupe in Hollywood, and Carmen Abbott wearing Spanish-era clothing; a man in costume.
  - Pasadena, ca. 1890-1931 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    Photographs. Images include: Hotel Raymond; Cawston Ostrich Farm (in operation from 1896-1931) in South Pasadena; El Molino Viejo (the Old Mill); Benjamin D. "Don Benito" Wilson and his residence; laborers making adobe bricks; and the trolley line running through San Marino, California (ca. 1905).
  - Livestock, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 6)
    Photographs of livestock on various rancho lands in California, including Baldwin Ranch on Rancho Santa Anita, the San Fernando Valley, and Santa Margarita Ranch.
  - San Bernardino, ca. 1900 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    Photographs. Images include: adobes; Urbita Springs (ca. 1905); trail to Camp Baldy in Upland; Smiley Heights, Redlands; Squirrel Inn, San Bernardino Mountains; Orange Street in Redlands following a parade for President Roosevelt (ca. 1903); Arrowhead Hot Springs Hotel in San Bernardino; City Park, San Bernardino; Santa Fe rail station; Elk's Clubhouse; Carnegie Library (ca. 1904); Masonic Temple; San Bernardino Business College; Courthouse; "I" Street in Colton (ca. 1907); E. Fourth and Third Streets in downtown San Bernardino; and the Frank Maddock residence at the Cajon Pass.
  - San Bernardino churches, ca. 1915 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    Photographs of various churches, including the First Methodist Episcopalian Church, San Bernardino Baptist Church, and a Catholic church.
  - San Gabriel, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 9)
    Photographs of Mt. Lowe, orange groves, and Mt. San Antonio.
  - Adobes, ca. 1880-1910 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    Photographs and notes pertaining to Southern California adobes and Sonora Town. Images include the General José Castro adobe; a San Gabriel adobe; a Pala adobe; Antonio Argüella adobe on Washington Street (ca. 1898); and the Casa Cahuenga adobe.
  - Valle de San Fernando, ca. 1880-1930 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    Assorted photographs and printed ephemera. Images include: Beale's Cut in the San Fernando Pass; Fremont Pass (also called Newhall Pass), which separated the Santa Susana and San Gabriel Mountains (ca. 1926); Rancho de los Encinos; old toll road; Cahuenga Pass (ca. 1890); Olive Walk at Mission San Fernando Rey (ca. 1894); and Valle de los Encinos near Mission San Fernando (ca. 1886).
  - Whittier, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 12)
    Duplicate photographs of Whittier, including the Whittier Lumber and Mill Co., San Pedro Lumber Co., and the San Jose hills.
  - Notebooks, ca. 1962 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    Notebooks containing Packman's research on Southern California history, including Spanish soldiers, Mission San Gabriel births and deaths, and ranchos. Includes a letter from Charles Puck, photographer.
  - Peralta family, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 14)
    Handwritten notes.
  - Dams, ca. 1952-1959 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    Clippings relating to the Frank Latta case and the Kernville Dam, and the 1928 break of the St. Francis Dam in Santa Clarita.
  - First Century Families, ca. 1960-1965 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    Clippings and printed ephemera for First Century Families events.
  - Genealogical research, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 2)
    Packman's research notes on the family histories of California's Spanish-Mexican and Anglo-American families, including the Sepulveda, Lopez, Carrillo, Pico, and Rimpau families.
  - Rancho maps and titles, ca. 1966 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    Photocopies of California Spanish-Mexican era rancho maps and an indenture agreement dated February 23, 1866 regarding the lands held at Ranchos Los Cerritos, San Pedro, Santa Gertrudes, Los Coyotes, and Los Alamitos.
  - Packman family photographs, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 4)
    Family photographs of the Packmans, including Ana Bégué de Packman, Julia Bégué de Pedroli, and Louisa Alaniz Bégué.
  - Notes and clippings, ca. 1930 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    Four typewritten pages of notes about Los Angeles-area photographs.
  - Leather Dollars: Short Stories of Pueblo Los Angeles (1 of 2), ca. 1932 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    Sample illustrations and suggested layouts. For oversize illustrations, additional photographs of the missions, and an article on branding, see box 13, folder 3.
  - Leather Dollars: Short Stories of Pueblo Los Angeles (1 of 2), ca. 1930-1940 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    Additional miscellaneous materials related to Leather Dollars. Includes a clipping about Mary Louise Packman, proofs, and publicity material for Early California Hospitality.
  - Ranchos (1 of 3), ca. 1952-1955 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    Printed ephemera, notes, maps, and a pamphlet by W.W. Robinson entitled The Old Spanish and Mexican Ranchos of Orange County.
  - Ranchos (2 of 3), ca. 1939-1940 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    Printed ephemera, including a small pamphlet by R. W. Brackett entitled History of the Ranchos of San Diego County; Packman's publication announcement for Early California Hospitality; and The Romance of the Ranchos by (E.) Palmer Conner.
  - Ranchos (3 of 3), ca. 1890-1925 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    Miscellaneous photographs, including a wine press in San Diego; Don Antonio Coronel and a woman dressed in Spanish-Mexican attire (ca. 1890); a group dressed in Spanish-Mexican attire at the Santa Maria adobe (ca. 1925); and Deputy Sheriff Edward in Spanish-Mexican attire.
  - Westwood--Miscellaneous research materials, ca. 1905-1940 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    Assorted research materials relelated to West Los Angeles, Westwood, and Santa Monica. Includes: photographs of Packman with Sheriff Eugene Biscailuz; exhibit copy; a photograph of the Sawtelle water supply dam in Sepulveda Canyon; materials on Rancho San Jose de Buenos Aires, including a photograph of Packman with Irvin S. Cobb; and materials on the National Soldiers' Home.
  - Westwood Bicentennial project, 1935, 1975-1976 (Box 13, Folder 1)